where are the
videos and it's a pretty fair question
so here's the website
skills. and you click on overview the
Boost and it's not completely obvious
where the videos are um the the videos
are actually hiding under here and this
whole schedule thing is going to get put
over here I'm just going to do that
right now but if you're reeing this
video it's because you forgot you didn't
know that all these blue things are
actually videos um as you click on them
these are almost always directly linked
to a video
there will be a couple cases where the
thing it links to is not a video but at
the at the current moment it everything
is video so that's where the videos are
just make sure you click on job started
Tech and somebody asked are we starting
with starting a career and that's a
valid question because for a very long
time you know we ended with that and and
this year in 2024 and from now on we're
going to start with outlining the
process of getting a job and then diving
into the specific skills uh that are
going to create the trust you need to
get the job so that's where the videos
are